http://www.shorrexpress.com/privacy-policy

National Packaging Programs
Managed Packaging Solutions (STAMP™)
Universal Robots Cobot Arms
Protective Packaging EquipmentProtective Packaging Equipment
National Packaging Programs
Managed Packaging Solutions (STAMP™)
Videos
COVID-19 UPDATE:We are open and continuing to support businesses during these unprecedented times.... »
Privacy Policy
This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) that applies to the domain(s) below. We refer to the website(s) accessible through the domain(s) and all related websites as “sites” and to each of them as a “site.”
shorr.com
When we refer to “we,” “us,” or “our,” we mean Hanchett Paper Company d/b/a Shorr Packaging Corporation, an Illinois corporation or the specific division, subsidiary, or affiliate that operates a site, provides its content, or processes information received through it, each as appropriate and applicable.
When we refer to “you” or “your,” we mean the person accessing the site. If the person accessing the site does so on behalf of, or for the purposes of, another person, including a business or other organization, “you” or “your” also means that other person, including a business organization.
This Privacy Policy does not cover information we collect by means other than a site. If you have any questions about how we use information collected by means other than a site, you should inquire at or before the time you give such information to us. Note that this Privacy Policy contains several important exceptions, most notably the exception involving use of information to identify and/or pursue persons who are under criminal investigation or who damage, or may damage, our information or other resources.
Please read this entire Privacy Policy to be sure that you understand these exceptions.
Information Ownership, Collection and Use
We are the sole owner of the information collected through the sites. We may collect information from users at several different points on a site. Based upon your usage of our sites, we may collect the following information: your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number and facts about your business.
This Privacy Policy addresses some types of information, means of collecting information, and uses of information that may not presently apply to one or more of the sites. We tell you about these types of information, means of collecting information, and uses of information anyway because we want to maintain flexibility in offering additional features without having to revisit this Privacy Policy every time we revise a site or offer new functions. No description of any type of information, means of collecting information, or use of information will require us to collect any particular information, make any particular use of any information, or offer any particular functionality through any site.
Ordering, Event Registration, and Related Processes
When and if you order products or services using a site or register for an event, we request information from you using an order form. When we already have information about you (such as through a previous order or registration, whether received through a site or otherwise), we may use such information to facilitate the order or registration process. When using an order form, you must provide contact information (such as name and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we use this contact information to contact you.
Child Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) Compliance and Related Information
The Child Online Privacy and Protection Act (COPPA) regulates online collection of information from persons under the age of 13. It is our policy to refrain from knowingly collecting or maintaining personally identifiable information relating to any person under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not supply any personally identifiable information through the sites. If you are under the age of 18 and have already provided personally identifiable information through the sites, please have your parent or guardian contact us immediately using the information below so that we can remove such information from our files.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the computer that runs an Internet browser. It can contain information about you, your computer, your browser, your session, the websites you visit, and other information about you or others who use, or have used, the computer or browser you use to access the Internet. The cookies we use, if any, are not linked to any personally identifiable information while using a site unless you have given us permission to link personally identifiable information to one or more cookies. You give us that permission any time you register on a site, place an order through a site, or identify yourself or the computer you are using through a site.
Most or all browsers permit you to disable or reject cookies. You can do this by setting the preferences in the browser. Use the “help” feature of your browser to obtain more information about refusing cookies.
If you set the browser you use to reject cookies, you can use the sites, but you may not be able to use the full functionality of one or more of the sites or it may take additional time to utilize such functionality.
Log Files
We or our hosting provider may collect traffic information from visitors for statistical analysis and site improvement. When you accesses a site, we or our hosting provider may collect information about your visit in a log file on a server. Log file information may include, but is not limited to, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We or our hosting provider use this information to analyze trends, administer sites, track users’ movements in the aggregate, and gather demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses and other log file information are not linked to personally identifiable information. We do not try to track users or to identify users individually except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, but we or our hosting provider do review this information to understand overall trends and to determine what kinds of content are popular and useful to users.
Sharing
(a) Aggregated information. We or our hosting provider may share aggregated demographic information with our users, our affiliated organizations, and other organizations with which we do, or contemplate doing, business. Such information is aggregated and is not linked to any information that can identify individual users.
(b) Outsourcing providers. We may use outside shipping or other outsourcing providers to process and ship orders or perform other functions. We use commercially reasonable diligence to restrict the purposes for which these outsourcing providers may use your personally identifiable information. The requirements or requests that we impose on such outsourcing providers vary with the sensitivity of the information and can, but do not necessarily, include requirements that these outsourcing providers not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes, except for backup and recovery operations. Although we use good faith efforts to impose, and/or ensure compliance by our outsourcing providers, we cannot, and will not, be responsible to users for misuse of personally identifiable information by such outsourcing providers. This is meant as a general description of our practices. It does not impose any duty upon us and it does not constitute a representation or warranty by us upon which you may rely.
(c) Specific services. We may have agreements with other parties to provide specific services. When you use such services, we may share personally identifiable information with such parties. In such cases, we will use good faith efforts to restrict the information provided to the information necessary for the provision of such services.
(d) General use. We share personally identifiable information (whether in return for compensation or otherwise) with various other vendors, suppliers, and advertisers. While we use good faith efforts to verify that such vendors, suppliers, and advertisers promote products and services of interest to site users, we cannot, and do not, endorse such vendors, suppliers, advertisers, products or services unless we expressly state otherwise. We share only such information as you yourself provide to us or someone else provides about you (such as through a registration process) and do not share personally identifiable information derived indirectly through IP address tracing or similar means. If you wish us to refrain from providing your personally identifiable information in this manner, please see the opt-out information and contact information provided below.
Links and Information Gathered by Others
One or more sites may contain links to other websites. We do not operate those other websites, and we cannot control the information that the operators of such other websites gather or what the operators of such other websites do with the information. We are therefore not responsible for the activities of the operators of such other websites. Since we do not control those other websites, you should review the privacy statement posted on these other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or practices of these other websites or their compliance with those privacy statements.
Newsletter
If you wish to subscribe to a newsletter we offer or to a mailing list that we maintain, we will collect from you contact information necessary to send the newsletter or other information to you. This is usually limited to your e-mail address, but may include other information.
Security
Where we collect nonpublic personal information from you, we or one or more of our service providers use industry-standard encryption and security standards to protect such information. You can tell whether encryption is being used by noting the “locked” or other status indicator on the browser you are using. If the browser you are using does not indicate that the session is secure (e.g. by displaying a lock, a key or another icon), you should assume that the connection is not secure and that third parties will receive the information shared by you and us during that part of the session.
We also use commercially reasonable efforts to protect user information offline. All sensitive user information is maintained in our offices or at the facilities of our information technology providers. We cause access to servers and connections to be limited by key or other access control. Only employees or agents who need the information to perform specific functions are granted access to personally identifiable information. We use reasonable efforts to ensure that our employees and agents are informed of our security and privacy practices.
Supplementation of Information
We sometimes supplement the information we receive from you with other information we receive from third party sources or clearinghouses. Thus, information we obtain through a site may be intermingled with and used in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than a site, including both offline and online sources.
Site and Service Updates
We may also send to you updates and service announcements about one or more of the sites. You may not un-subscribe or opt not to receive such announcements because such announcements contain important information about the services offered through the relevant sites.
Misappropriation of Personal Information
For the purposes of any applicable law regarding notification of persons whose personal information was, or is reasonably believed to have been, acquired by an unauthorized person, our information security policy provides that any required notification may, where permitted by law, be made by the use of e-mail, telephone, fax, mail (including a notice printed in an available area of a bill or statement) or posting a notice on a site. The specific means used is up to us and we will use our judgment based on the circumstances. Where any notice is to be sent to a specific address or number (such as e-mail address, physical address, telephone number, etc.), we will use the latest available address in our records. EXCEPT TO THE EXTENT PROHIBITED BY LAW, YOU AGREE TO THIS MEANS OF NOTIFICATION.
Correcting or Updating Personal Information
If your personal information changes, if you have reason to believe that your personal information as we maintain it is incorrect, or if you no longer desire service, you may contact using the contact information below and we will accommodate all reasonable requests for such changes.
Choice/Opt-out
Users who no longer wish to receive newsletters or promotional materials or have their information provided to third parties may opt to not receive such communications or have information shared by contacting us using the information below. We will comply with such requests as soon as is commercially practicable. Such compliance may involve batch processing and other processes that take 30 days or longer. If you opt not to receive such communications or allow us to share your information and then give your personal information to us again using a site or under other circumstances that permit us to use your information, we will regard your opt-out as rescinded.
In most cases, it is impractical for us to stop any other party to whom we have supplied your information from continuing to use the information and opting out will usually not stop others to whom we have provided your information from continuing to use it. To change your preference with regard to the way your information is treated: email Shorr Packaging
Response Times
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to timely make any changes you request. Many such changes are accomplished using batch processing (i.e. collecting a number of similar change requests and making all such changes at once), so the changes may not be immediately effective. If you require an immediate change to your personally identifiable information and are unable to make such a change using the available site resources, please contact us.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change, modify, or update this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. We indicate the date of the current Privacy Policy below, so you know when it was last updated. Continued use of a site after any such revision or modification constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as so revised or modified.
If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on one or more sites and/or other places we deem appropriate. Except as stated below, we will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected. If we decide to use information about you in a manner different from that stated in the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of collection, we will notify you by e-mail if, and to the extent that, you have provided your e-mail address. If you reply to such an e-mail within a reasonable time and request that we not use your personally identifiable information in the proposed new manner, we will honor your request, but we reserve the right to suspend your access to all or part of the services offered through one or more sites if you do so. If you do not reply to such an e-mail, or we receive a reply of “undeliverable” or similar message from your last known e-mail address, in either case after a reasonable time, we will use the information in the proposed new manner.
BY USING A SITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS CHANGE PROCEDURE.
Exceptions
Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we may collect personally identifiable information and use such information in ways other than those described above if we are required to do so by law or if we deem it advisable in the course of assisting law enforcement activities or protecting the sites or other property. Without limiting the foregoing, we reserve the right to use and disclose any information that you provide to us if we deem it advisable in the prosecution or defense of any litigation involving your use of any site.
Contact Information
If you feel that we are not abiding by this Privacy Policy or if you have questions regarding the Privacy Policy, you may contact our privacy liaison using the following information. Additionally, If you (a) wish to begin or end receipt of newsletters or promotional information (b) wish to update your user information, or (c) wish to opt in or out of any other service offered through the site, please contact our technical personnel using the following information. Please be sure to include your name and your user name (if applicable), but do not include any information regarding your password(s), if any.
BILL BONACCORSI
Shorr Packaging Corp
4000 Ferry Rd,
Aurora, IL 60502
630-499-3020
Email Privacy Liaison
Transfer of Business Assets
The personal information you provide is considered a company asset and may be included among transferred assets if we or any of our subsidiaries or affiliates or any of their assets is ever acquired by a third party.
Clickstream Data
As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as "clickstream data," can be collected and stored by a web sites’ server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the web site from which you linked to a site. We may use clickstream data as a form of non-personally identifiable information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of a site, how visitors navigate throughout a site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information will only be used to improve the sites. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregated.
Discussion and Community Tools
We may, from time to time, make chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups and other community tools available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information for other users to view and for us to use. For example, from time to time, we may use the content you write (including your name or screen name if you post it) for promotional purposes, in e-mail newsletters or elsewhere, and by using a site and/or these chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups, and other community tools, you agree that we may do so. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas, since anyone - not just us - may use publicly posted information.
International Users
If you are visiting a site from outside of the United States, your connection may be through and to servers located in the United States, your registration, entries and orders placed through a site may be fully processed in and shipped from the United States and all information you provide may be processed and maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using a site, you authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. This Privacy Policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of the State of Illinois and the USA, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the USA in the State of Illinois as provided in our Terms of Use.
Use and Disclosure of anonymous Information
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze how our site is used, as well as to offer you products, programs or services. Sometimes we share aggregated information with others, including affiliated companies and non-affiliated companies.
Get More Info
Have Questions? Need Help?
© 2020 Hanchett Paper Company. All rights reserved.
Protective Packaging EquipmentProtective Packaging Equipment
Managed Packaging Solutions (STAMP™)
